真探
第二季 第二集
為什麼這裡會有水漬
How'd a water stain get there?
今年只下過一兩場雨
It rained maybe twice this last year.
好像所有東西都是紙糊的一樣
It's like everything's Papier-mache?
別想了
Stop thinking.
我不喜歡受制於人
I don't like being on a ledge.
沒有人只靠自己的錢就能富起來
Nobody gets rich on their own money.
我從來沒弄懂該拿它怎麼辦
I never really knew what to do with it.
錢
Money.
看著它就像看到了自己
I see that about myself.
你總是說想要擁有大片土地
You always said you want lots of land.
是的
Yes,
可是你需要有子女來繼承這些
but you need children to leave it to.
這些並不真正屬於你
It's never really yours.
生不帶來死不帶去
You don't take it with you.
死了的話什麼也帶不走
You don't take anything with you.
孑然一身 身無長物
Just yourself, whatever that was.
就像你一樣 我辛勞一生
I've worked my whole life, same as you.
幸運地躋身富人階級
And not being poor is better than the opposite.
當年在芝加哥的時候
My old man back in Chicago,
我還小
when I was a kid...
我爸去喝酒的時候總會把我鎖進地下室
he used to lock me in the basement when he'd go on a bender.
通常會鎖一晚上
Usually last the night.
第二天再放我出來
Let me out the next day.
我猜他是想保證我的安全
Thought he was keeping me safe, I guess.
有一次 我六歲
This one time, I was six...
他把我鎖在地下室
he puts me down there
我醒過來
and I wake up
發現還是鎖著的
and it's locked.
以前也發生過這種事
It had happened before.
反正 我猜他被警察抓了
Anyways, I guess he ended up arrested.
我猜的
I guess.
天啊 可憐的孩子
God, baby.
第二天早上
By the second morning...
我就沒有吃的了
I was out of food.
第三天 燈泡燒壞了
The third day, the lightbulb burned out.
裡面漆黑一片
Pitch-black in there.
然後又有了老鼠
That's when the rats started coming out.
我正打著瞌睡
I dozed off and...
感覺到有東西在啃我的指頭
I felt the thing, you know, nibbling my finger.
我醒過來
I woke up.
老鼠正在啃我的指頭
It was, you know, chewing my finger.
你做了什麼
What did you do?
我在黑暗中伸出雙手抓住它
I grabbed it in the dark with my hands
然後往地上砸
and I started smashing it.
一直砸一直砸
And I just kept smashing it...
砸到最後手裡只剩下一團碎肉
till it was nothing but goo in my hands.
我在裡面又待了兩天
Two more days I was in there...
在黑暗裡
in the dark...
直到我爸回了家
till my dad comes home.
有時候我真想知道你還經歷過多少
Sometimes I wonder how many things you have like that...
我不知道的事
that I don't know about.
從那時起 我就在想
Ever since, I wondered
如果他沒回家呢
what if he never comes home?
如果我
What if I'm...
還被關在地下室裡
still in that basement
身處黑暗中呢
in the dark?
如果我死在那裡了呢
What if I died there?
這個讓我想到了那些日子
That's what that reminds me of.
什麼
What?
那片水漬
That water stain.
有東西在告訴我
Something's trying to tell me that
這些都是紙餬
it's all Papier-mache.
有東西想要喚醒我
Something's telling me to wake up.
就像
Like...
就像我並非真實存在
like I'm not real.
就像我是在做夢
Like I'm only dreaming.
死亡時間在26號早上4點到9點之間
TOD between 4:00 and 9:00 A.M. morning of the 26th.
毒檢顯示有鎮靜劑 酒精
Tox shows Xanax, alcohol,
死者還患有淋病
also had gonorrhea, for what it's worth.
他眼中有鹽酸
Hydrochloric acid on his eyes.
燒灼痕跡顯示他當時仰躺
Burn pattern tells us he was on his back.
眼眶周圍沒有飛濺痕跡說明滴入得很精準
Lack of spray around the orbital cavity indicates precision.
也許是用某種玻璃制眼部滴管
Some kind of glass eyedropper, maybe.
這屍體是我們的
He's our body.
這一點不會變 所以不如你們先介紹下情況
I don't see that changing, so why don't you all fill me in?
受害者是一起州調查案中的關鍵人物
Victim is a key figure in a state's investigation.
-什麼州調查案 -新立案的
-What state investigation? -Newly formed.
我們在調查媒體針對
We're looking into various allegations
芬奇警局提出的多項指控
made against Vinci in the papers.
芬奇的警探曾將卡史伯雷
Vinci detectives have been on Caspere
作為失蹤人口調查了兩天
as a missing person for two days.
他的房子遭到過入室搶劫
We have the man's house which was burglarized.
你們要是想阻止我們的話
You want to shut us out,
我們將匿名繼續我們的調查
we'll continue our investigation autonomously.
在芬奇
In Vinci,
這樣所有人都能保留他們自己的小秘密
so everybody can keep their little corners to themselves,
但是 女士們先生們 警局正在調查本案
but, ladies and gentlemen, PD is solving this case.
文圖拉我能理解 但是這和州有什麼關係
I understand Ventura. How does the state have any claim here?
我們的警員找到了屍體
Our officer found the body.
這可以把你從那事裡救出來 伍卓夫
This could get you out from under, Woodrugh.
那個女演員的事
That actress bullshit.
你將會作為州調查員參與此案
You'd be detailed as a state's investigator.
你表面上的任務是調查卡史伯雷被害一案
The Caspere homicide is your public investigation.
而調查芬奇警局是你的秘密任務
Looking into Vinci PD is your confidential mandate.
為送出大陪審團審判收集訊息
Gathering intel for a grand jury.
這次調查對州政府很重要
This probe is very important to the governor's office.
就算按你說的做了
Say this goes your way.
事後對我的人有什麼好處
How's it play for my boy here once the dust settles?
一切都順利
Everything shakes out,
將給你提供一個繼續任職調查員的機會
you'll be offered a chance to remain investigator.
也許還能榮升州探員
In line for a state detective shield.
我們可以抹掉行政上的所有麻煩
We can wipe away all that admin hassle.
等這事過去
When this is over,
我就想繼續回去當騎警
can I just go back to being on the bike?
手腕和腳踝處可以看到明顯擦傷
You can see abrasions on his wrists and ankles,
軀幹上還有瘀傷
lividity on his torso.
他被倒吊起來過
He was bound upside down.
或者類似姿勢
Or close to it.
地方檢察官很在意芬奇警局
Attorney General's office has concerns about obfuscation
混亂的狀況
on the part of Vinci PD.
貝瑟瑞警探 你是這支隊伍的首席指揮官
Detective Bezzerides, you'll be primary commander of the detail.
第二指揮官是芬奇來的那傢伙 韋科洛
Secondary is gonna be a Vinci guy, Velcoro.
遇害者和大筆洛杉磯縣政府資金有牽連
Your DB was into a lot of LA County money.
他的房間被闖入 所以你要去趟芬奇
His house was broken into, so you're going to Vinci.
和你搭檔的芬奇警探 據說很腐敗
Vinci detective with you, word is he's bent.
接近他 想辦法策反他
Work him. Leverage something to turn him.
一周內我們就會展開全面調查
We'll have a full state probe up inside a week.
卡史伯雷的死是整個事件的切入口
Caspere's death is a window into everything.
整個事件是什麼
And what is everything exactly?
你瞭解芬奇市嗎？
You know anything about the City of Vinci?
二十世紀初 那裡是罪犯的天堂
It started out as a vice haven early 1900s.
在二十年代進入了工業化
Went industrial in the '20s.
把居民趕出了工業區
Pushed out residents from manufacturing zones.
是全州污染最嚴重的區域
Worse air polluter in the state.
每年生產排放一千兩百萬公斤有毒廢物
Annually emits or processes 27 million pounds of toxic waste.
共和黨當初想阻止我祖父進行
Reds tries to stop my grandfather
工業區域二次規劃
from industrial rezoning.
現在也一樣
Same thing.
自上次贏了環保局訴訟案後蓋爾多夫一直糾纏不休
Geldof's been after us since we won the last EPA suit.
都是為了錢 韋科洛警探
It's about money, Detective Velcoro.
卡史伯雷是社區
Caspere was one of the architects
重建計劃中的建築師之一
of the community renewal initiative.
通過立法
Passing legislature,
八年來我們市能
our city gets to keep 75%
保留近75%的稅收收入
of its county tax revenue for eight years.
-那是多少 -大概九百萬美金
-And what's that worth? -About $900 million.
並未算進一般政府資金
Being kept from the county general fund.
恩斯特 那就是我們的錢了
Hell, Ernst, it's our money.
在經濟衰退中 芬奇可書寫了神話
Vinci's a goddamn success story in a depressed economy.
州政府會通過這次謀殺案
State's gonna use the homicide to dig into
把這裡查個底朝天 雷
whatever they can, Ray.
卡史伯雷的案子查到哪 你就得跟到哪
Wherever the Caspere case goes, we need you running point.
控制好度 控制流出的訊息
Control the sprawl. Control the flow of information.
芬奇警局你下來就是狄克遜了
Dixon is secondary to you staging out of Vinci.
你會給掌管這個專案組的
You'll be working under a Ventura detective
文圖拉市的警探做副手
commanding the task force.
清楚了嗎 警探
That clear to you, Detective?
收到 副隊 只有一個問題
10-4, Lieutenant. Just one question.
我到底要不要破案
Am I supposed to solve this or not?
只要隨時聯絡就好 韋科洛警探
Just no surprises, Detective Velcoro.
雷明白需要優先考慮
Ray accepts dualities must be effected
公眾利益
to serve public interests.
確實
I really do.
-為什麼說被吊起來過 -纖維痕跡
-Bound? -Vinyl fabric.
兩個手腕明顯可見皮帶扣的印痕
You can see the edge of the buckle's imprint on both wrists.
還有膠帶的痕跡
Tape residue.
骨盆處傷口是由12口徑散彈槍近距離施射造成的
Pelvic wounds are from a 12-gauge at point-blank range.
算是相當大的傷口了
Some kind of Super-X heavy load.
是眼睛受傷後的事
Came after the eye stuff.
官方死因是心臟病 創傷性心臟病
Official COD is heart attack. Trauma-induced.
致命一擊
A coup de grace.
瘀傷顯示死亡後
Lividity indicates he was placed
他被人為放置成了直立狀態
in upright position after death.
維持了數小時
Spent a few hours that way.
指甲裡沒有痕跡 也沒有指紋
Nothing under his nails, no prints.
完全沒有痕跡嗎？
No trace at all?
眼睛 這是什麼可惡手法啊
His eyes? What the fuck kind of modus operandi is that?
醫生說是鹽酸造成的
Doc said it was hydrochloric acid.
還用了散彈槍
And a shotgun blast happened.
拷問 有人想從他那裡得到訊息
Torture. Somebody wanted to know something.
他的房子也被翻了一遍
Yeah, his house was tossed.
有人開始行動了
Somebody's making a move.
什麼 什麼意思
What? What does that mean?
你認識卡史伯雷
You knew Caspere?
北部在進行一些交易
There's deals being done upstate.
-大量資金在運轉 -什麼交易
-A lot of money moving around. -What deals?
-探我的底 是這樣嗎 -法蘭克
-You pull my string? Is that how this works? -Jesus, Frank.
我知道的越多 就越好處理事情
The more I know, the better I can deal with this.
這就是你該處理的事
This is what you deal with.
卡史伯雷對我在做的事很重要
Caspere was important to this thing I have going on.
現在我得把這事處理乾淨
I've got to clean it up now.
所以你要仔細調查直到查清為止
So you beat the bushes until you figure it out.
你已經又不是警長的小跟班了 你是一名警探
You ain't no sheriff's brownie. You're a detective.
你最好的線人是誰
Who's your best informant?
你真的假的啊
Are you serious?
去死吧 雷蒙德
Fucking hell, Raymond.
走開
Vaya!
危險
Peligro.
是啊是啊 你媽的
Yeah, yeah, that's right. Fuck me.
很高興見到你
So good to see you.
你怎麼不常來
Why don't you visit me more?
很忙 要工作
Just busy. The job.
工作啊 我們很久沒一起吃飯了
The job. We haven't had dinner in ages.
所以我給你帶了這個 媽
That's why I brought you this, Ma.
別跟我套交情
Don't give me that Ma shit.
現在開始也太晚了
It's too late for us to start all that now.
你得吃點東西
Well, you ought to eat something.
我不要麵包糠
Oh, I don't touch bread.
幫我把皮剝掉 保利
Peel that skin off for me, Paulie.
太結實了
So strong.
我前些天看到了你過去的舞伴
I saw your old prom date the other day.
她發胖了
She got fat.
我記得她
I remember her.
等不及要跟男人上床
Couldn't wait to have somebody's baby.
她人很好 對我很好
She was nice. She was nice to me.
所有妹子都對你很好 保利
All the girls are nice to you, Paulie.
你現在還沒察覺出來嗎？
You haven't figured that out by now?
今晚想留下嗎？
Want to stay tonight?
我們可以看個克林特[美國演員]的電影
We can watch a Clint movie.
你可以住你以前的房間
You can have your old room.
我還有事
I'm working on something.
-只是來看看 -她是誰 你個小壞蛋
-Just came to see... -Who is she, you scamp?
放盪的混蛋
You rake.
這一點你跟你老爸一模一樣
You got hound's blood just like your daddy.
我可能有段時間不會回來
I'm not gonna be around for a while.
要去洛杉磯還有海岸附近工作
I've got to work around LA and the coast.
特別小組
Special detail.
那就留下吧 我們可以玩牌
Then stay. We can play cards.
你可以住你以前的房間
You can have your old room.
你最近有在餐館上班嗎？
You been getting any more shifts at the restaurant lately?
沒 我有腕管綜合征
Not with my carpal tunnel.
反正我也會失去救濟
I'd lose my state check anyway.
我以為比爾會讓你打黑工
I thought Bill was letting you work off the books.
比爾 別跟我提那個混蛋
Oh, Bill? Don't talk to me about that motherfucker.
你要放棄你自己嗎？
Are you gonna give yourself up...
還是要來硬的
or do this the hard way?
對我來說都不容易
There ain't no easy with me.
你知道的
You know that.
該死 我討厭弄得一團糟
Damn. I so hate making a mess.
太多書面工作 你知道的
A lot of paperwork, you know.
那會毀了你
It messes with you.
去死 我服過刑了
Screw you. I did my time in prison.
我們在根據保險審計列出房內物品
We're listing contents against insurance audits.
看是什麼被偷了
See what was stolen.
有人在找什麼東西
Well, somebody was looking for something.
也就解釋了為什麼會拷問他
Would explain the torture.
也許吧 這人還真是總想著做愛啊
Maybe. Guy really thought about fucking a lot.
你能不敲了嗎？
Do you mind?
心理醫生的預約
Psychiatrist appointments.
他在看心理醫生
He was seeing a shrink.
我們得給日程表上的每一個預約打電話
We need to call every appointment in that calendar.
把這些圈住的日期跟他的GPS記錄進行比對
Should check all those circled dates against his GPS.
好
Yeah.
那電子煙跟你還真搭 很多人都不行
You pull off that e-cig. Not a lot of people do.
這個地方每天都有七萬人湧入 對嗎？
This place gets a day-to-day influx of 70,000 people, right?
他們都住在那裡
Where do they live?
我也試過電子煙 感覺是它在抽我
I tried one once. It felt like it was smoking me.
真煙不會讓你有那樣的感覺
A real cigarette wouldn't make you feel like that.
也許那有點太像
Maybe it was just a little too close to
吸一個機器屌 我也說不好
sucking a robot's dick. I don't know.
卡史伯雷是我的主要投資人
Caspere was my bank on this thing.
我的垃圾處理公司建的這裡
My disposal company set this up.
處理化學廢產品 我們冒了風險
Chemical runoff. We took the risk.
那風險讓你有機會買入中央鐵路走廊
And that risk afforded you the chance to buy into the corridor.
但我要說的是 收購沒有完成
But I'm telling you, that buy was never made.
卡史伯雷讓我付了蒙特利十二個地塊的錢
Caspere had me down for 12 parcels below Monterey.
法蘭克 我只能將卡史伯雷
Frank, I can only account for
已經完成的交易列入預算
what purchases Caspere completed.
-你是說 -麥坎德利斯先生
-Are you saying that I---Mr. McCandless,
卡史伯雷先生以短期控股公司的身份
Mr. Caspere had effectively sold Mr. Semyon the land
已經將土地賣給了塞米恩先生
while acting as a short-term holding company.
儘管卡史伯雷遭遇不幸 我們想做的只是
All we're trying to do is ensure the deal
保證我們的土地交易
for our parcel goes through despite Caspere's tragedy.
如果這筆交易有合法記錄
If you got this transaction legally documented,
-就不會有問題 -你知道我們有難處
-it shouldn't be hard. -You know we have issues.
如果我們有他媽的書面記錄
If we had a fucking paper trail,
我們就能通過銀行處理了
we'd be doing this through banks.
那我只能說你的處境非常不妙
Well, otherwise I'd say you're in the unenviable position
一個死人欠了你的錢
of being owed money by a dead man.
那可是我的五百萬美元啊
That's $5 million of my money.
等一下 我們的理解是
Hold it, we were given to understand
我們的合作夥伴是卡特拉史特
that our partnership was with Catalast.
如果卡史伯雷先生付了款 那確實如此
Had Mr. Caspere made payment, it would have been.
你的名字也會被新增在負責開發的
And your name would have been added to the corporate charter
公司名單上
for the development.
-但他沒有 -我怎麼知道這是真的
-But he didn't. -How do I know that?
我們不是混混 法蘭克
We're not gangsters, Frank.
這我們不能接受
This is unacceptable.
既然卡史伯雷的條件已經無效
Since Caspere's remaining interests have been voided,
我可以給你同樣的土地 同樣的價錢
I can provide you the same parcel, same price.
-七百萬美金 -同樣
-Seven million. -The same?
報給我們的是一千萬
We were quoted 10.
不是我報的
Not by me.
混蛋
Motherfuck.
王八蛋
Motherfuck me.
我們賣了芬奇的資產投給卡史伯雷和...
We sold off our Vinci assets to put in with Caspere and...
為了這筆交易我全部變現了
I went liquid for this deal.
我能說什麼 法蘭克 聽著就像
What can I tell you, Frank? It sounds like
卡史伯雷先生在拿你的錢當兒戲
Mr. Caspere was playing fast and loose with your capital.
我能再次提供補償買進
I can offer you the buy-in again,
但你似乎缺錢
but it sounds like you're short.
我可以再拿回來
I can get it back.
再找筆錢 會值得的
Find another stake, it'd be worth your while.
失陪了
Excuse me.
該死 他說七百萬
Shit. Seven he says?
這個時候七百萬對我來說和一千萬一樣
Seven's the same as 10 to me at this point.
都不能捨掉零
Can't round off zero.
我被削弱了嗎？
Am I diminished?
那是我要告訴該死的...
Is that my message to the goddamn...
我的合作夥伴拿走了我的錢
My business partner takes my money,
被拷問並殺害了
gets tortured and murdered,
然後呢
and what?
我等著這位韋科洛把這變得像羅克福德嗎？
I'm waiting on this Velcoro burnout to make like Rockford?
通知所有人
Get everybody.
史坦 伊瓦爾 他表親 我們格蘭岱爾人
Stan, Ivar, his cousins, our Glendale people.
他媽的布萊克 不管他去哪裡了
Fucking Blake, wherever the fuck he's been.
法蘭克 我們可以看一下你的剩餘資產
Frank, we can look at your remaining assets.
我什麼都沒了
I don't have any fucking assets.
房子和賭場都被雙倍抵押了
The house and the poker room were double mortgaged.
這就是他媽的全部
This was fucking everything.
你是這個意思 法蘭克 為什麼
That's what you meant. Frank, why did you--
別管了 我會再拿回來的
Leave it. I'll get it back.
每一分錢
Every dime.
大概是一個月前
That was maybe a month ago.
九月
September.
慶祝紅延線破土動工
Celebrated breaking ground on the Red Line extension
和即將製作的一部好萊塢大電影
and the imminent production of a major Hollywood movie.
城市的頭條新聞 班參與了...
Big news for the city. And Ben had a hand--
你能告訴我們卡史伯雷先生
Could you tell us anything about
在聚會上的行為舉止嗎？
Mr. Caspere's demeanor at the party?
他和誰在一起嗎 女伴
Was he with someone? A date?
他最近在約會的一個女人
A woman he had been seeing.
我覺得是
I think.
不太記得她名字了
Can't quite recall her name.
-恩斯特 -我記得是塔莎小姐 先生
-Ernst? -A Miss Tascha, I believe, sir.
他和很多女孩約會嗎 多到你不知道名字
He see a lot of girls? Enough you wouldn't know her name?
班的社交生活很活躍
I believe Ben maintained an active social life.
那方面我們沒什麼交集
We didn't often cross paths that way.
我們只是一起處理公事
We only met over business.
你有沒有可能有那次聚會的照片呢 先生
You wouldn't have any pictures from the party, sir, by any chance?
能幫助我們找到那個女孩的東西
Something to help us identify the girl.
卡史伯雷對他的社區很敬業
Mr. Caspere was dedicated to his community.
95個居民的社區
A community of 95 residents.
你上次見他時他看起來有在為什麼事煩惱嗎？
He didn't seem distressed by anything last you saw him?
沒有 只是讓人頭痛的老問題
No, just the usual headaches.
縣裡不能原諒我們的獨立
County can't forgive our independence.
除了一起工作你也不怎麼和他聊
And you didn't talk to him much outside of business get-togethers?
還有偶爾的內閣會議
And cabinet meetings occasionally.
好吧
Well...
謝謝你 閣下 很有幫助
Thank you, Your Honor. That'll do us.
你記得聚會那晚
Do you recall what time
卡史伯雷先生幾點離開你家的嗎？
Mr. Caspere left your house night of the party?
11點左右 也可能是12點
I believe around 11:00, maybe 12:00.
-大概是結束的時候 -和塔莎小姐一起
-Around the time things broke up. -With Miss Tascha?
謝謝你 閣下
Thank you, Your Honor.
謝謝你們 警探
Thank you, Detective.
我希望這案子盡快解決
I'd like to see this solved as soon as possible.
拿到了他的銀行記錄 電話
Got his bank records, phone calls.
但還不知道他於此有沒有關係
Don't know if he had any of the lines, though.
開始覺得他一定有別的帳戶
Starting to think he must have kept other accounts.
小子 匯報時再說吧
Hey, kid, just save it for the debrief.
你為什麼在這裡
Why are you here?
你甚至都不是調查員 對嗎？
You're not even an investigator, right?
特別小組 這案子歸州里管
Special detail. State owns the case.
還找到了他的律師
Found his lawyer, too.
為這破事不得不跑遍洛杉磯
Had to hump all over LA for this shit.
還有銀行的那個死基佬
Oh, and this one fag at the bank
好像要挑逗我
tried, like, hitting on me.
差點揍了這傢伙
Almost clocked the guy.
是嗎 你為什麼要那樣做
Yeah? Why would you do that?
我沒惡意 種馬
Hey, no trouble here, stud.
別把我攪和進去 好嗎？
Just leave me out of it, all right?
這些是他保險公司提供的表單
His insurance had these forms.
可能是卡史伯雷被盜的東西
Items likely stolen from Caspere's place,
我們可以去各個當鋪查檢查
we can put out pawn sheets on them.
你們查到什麼了
What'd you guys get?
這個年輕人 他有爆炸消息
The young man here, he got a dynamite anecdote.
上次提款是五天前
Last withdrawal was five days ago.
除了這次都很規律
Nothing jumps except this.
每月一次 一次4000美元
Once a month, $4,000 cash withdrawal.
讓我看看
Let me see this.
提款好像都是在
The withdrawals seem to come around the time
他日程表的空白時間裡
of these blank days in his calendar.
-你拿到他的GPS記錄了嗎 -嗯
-Did you get his GPS? -Yeah.
給
Here.
這些日期什麼都沒有
There's nothing on those dates.
車哪裡都沒去 他的梅賽德斯是租的
Car didn't go anywhere. Says his Mercedes was a lease.
這就說得通了
Well, that makes sense.
不是市政 是卡特拉史特集團
Not city. Catalast Group.
卡特拉史特為什麼要幫他租車
Why'd Catalast lease him a car?
也許有人該打電話問問
Maybe somebody should call them.
你跟他關係很好嗎？
You tight with him?
我跟誰都不怎麼樣
I'm not tight with anybody.
我能明天再繼續嗎？
Can I pick up here tomorrow?
當然
Sure.
我先走了
I gotta go.
-怎麼了 -這些坐標
-What? -These coordinates.
全都在北邊
They're up north.
蒙特利縣 夫勒史諾市 吉爾羅伊
Monterey County, Fresno, Gilroy.
大多都是週末去的
A lot of them on weekends.
查德呢
Where's Chad?
他不會來了
He's not coming.
怎麼了 為什麼
What? Why?
你居然還有臉問為什麼
You're gonna ask me why? Really?
你這個變態
You fucking prick.
怎麼 你是說學校那事嗎？
What, that thing at the school?
我向查德道過歉了 而且這是我倆之間的事
I apologized to Chad and it's between me and him.
不光是這件事 你心裡明白
That's not the end of the story and you know it.
-還有什麼 -警察說有人打了威特·康羅伊
-How's that? -The police said that someone beat up Wit Conroy.
說他被打與發生在學校的某些爭執有關
Said it had something to do with a schoolyard altercation.
我不清楚是怎麼回事
Well, I don't know anything about that,
但有時候孩子不打不成器
but sometimes a good beating provokes personal growth.
你也不會幹別的了 是嗎？
It's not like you know any other way, right?
該死的
God damn it.
查德跟你在一起時總是很焦慮
Chad gets anxious when he has to be around you.
你知道嗎 你都沒有察覺吧
Do you get that? Do you even see it?
胡扯 我 我們會聊天
That's bullshit. I--we talk,
我們會一起搭模型 給彼此寫信
we build models, we write letters,
我還給他買了錄音筆
I got him this recorder.
可是他給你回過幾次信
And how many times has he written you back?
他需要我 好嗎 只是他自己還沒意識到
He needs me, all right, even if he doesn't know it.
如果他感到焦慮 可能只是因為他知道
And if he gets anxious, it's probably because he knows
他又得聽他媽說他爸的壞話了
he's gonna have to listen to his mom talk shit about his dad.
沒錯 你就是很壞 雷
Yeah. You're bad, Ray.
你是個混蛋
You're a bad person.
-你的存在對我兒子沒有好處 -別這麼說
-And you're bad for my son. -Don't say that.
你是瞭解我的
You know me.
我們曾經相愛 而且
We had something and--
自從我為你做了那件事 情況就失控了
What I done for you, things started to slip away from me--
不 你做那件事不是為了我 雷
No, you didn't do that for me, Ray.
別說那是為我做的
Don't you dare say that you did that for me.
我有權見我兒子
I had a right by any natural law.
我有權力
I had a right.
我來就是想當面跟你說這事
I came to tell you this in person.
理查本不想讓我來的
Richard didn't want me to.
我申請了監督探訪的緊急條令
I'm getting an emergency writ for supervised visits.
你說什麼 不
What? No.
我們正在申請單獨監護權
We're petitioning for sole custody.
什麼
What?
為什麼
No, why?
因為我們不能再這樣下去了
Because this can't go on.
真的不能
It can't.
看看你自己吧
I mean, look at yourself.
你不能 求你了 求求你 不要
You will not--no. Please, please, don't.
你以前是很正派的
You used to have something, a decency.
你曾經非常正派
You were good at being decent
直到有事發生
until something happened.
倘若周圍一切安好 你便安好
You were fine as long as everything else was fine.
但是一旦有事發生
But then something happened
你就完全變了一個人
and you weren't strong enough to stay decent.
-現在 -你別想就這麼跑了
-And now---You won't get away with it.
我會把整座城市燒成灰燼
I will burn this entire fucking city to the ground first.
我還會申請親子鑑定 雷
I'll petition for a paternity test, too, Ray.
-如果你再逼我 -不 求你 別這樣
-If you make me. -Don't. Please. Please, don't.
不要做親子鑑定 求你了
Don't do that, please.
該死的 他是我的一切...
God damn it, look, he's--he's all I--
我承認 我是個人渣
all right, I'm a piece of shit,
但那孩子對我這糟爛的一生來說意味著一切
but that boy is all I have in my entire shitty life.
是嗎？
No, babe.
那你明白他應該過更好的生活吧
Then don't you know he deserves better?
我操 我操他媽的
Oh, fuck. Son of a bitch.
我的車被人追尾了 你這混
Some asshole just rear-ended my car. Look, you mother--ah!
操
Fuck.
我操
Son of--
他媽的
Oh, fuck.
下次 我們會把你裝到後車箱裡
Next time, we put you in trunk.
我操
Oh, fuck!
天哪 老兄 這是怎麼回事
Jesus, buddy. What was that about?
上帝 謝謝你 我操他媽的
Oh, God, thank you. Fuckin' me--
那些人為什麼要這樣對你
Why would somebody come after you like that, guy?
簡直太瘋狂了 是不是
I mean, that was crazy, right?
我不知道 他們
I don't know. They just--
你做過什麼得罪人的事嗎？
What did you do to piss somebody off?
-能想起來嗎 -你這話是什麼意思
-Can you think of anything? -What does that mean?
我也不知道 我問你呢
I don't know what that means. I'm asking you.
你做過什麼 讓那些人如此對你
What you might have did to get guys like that after you.
等一下 我認識你嗎？
Wait, do I know you?
我從沒見過你 我只是看到了事情的經過
I've never seen you before, but I saw the whole thing.
我希望我們能弄清楚你到底做了什麼
And I wish we could figure out what you did.
是不是你的某些行為
Like some kind of behavior
讓那些人看不慣了
that guys like that would have issue with.
比如頂撞了他們 朝他們豎了中指
Like mouthed off or made a gesture
或者在芬奇的血汗工廠裡管賬
or you run a book in Vinci sweatshops.
什麼 就是因為這個嗎？
What? Is that what this is?
因為什麼 跟你想的一樣嗎？
Is what what what is? Is that what you think this is?
反正我看你像是惹了什麼不該惹的人
It just seems to me like you pissed off some serious people.
你應該多加小心
Maybe you ought to take more care.
好好想想吧 朋友
Just a thought, pal.
韋科洛和貝瑟瑞來拜訪皮特勒醫生
Velcoro and Bezzerides to see Dr. Pitlor.
我們預約過
We called ahead.
你們這做手術嗎？
You do surgeries here?
只是整容手術
Only cosmetic.
本診所有一組專業的醫務人員
The clinic employs a small group of medical professionals
提供多種服務
who cover a variety of services.
這太震驚了
This is quite a shock.
他和你提過麻煩 敵人
Anything he might have told you that indicated
之類的嗎？
trouble, enemies?
這家診所名聲在外 全靠謹言慎行 警官
The reputation of this clinic rests on its discretion, Officers.
就是保密
Confidentiality.
你的患者被人謀殺了
Your patient was murdered.
他沒有家人
He's got no living family.
有人用酸燒了他的眼睛 醫生
Somebody burned out his eyes with acid, Doc.
我當然願意提供幫助
Well, of course I am willing to help.
至少我希望能幫上忙
I would hope I can, at least.
他在這裡接受哪方面治療
What were you treating him for?
很多 神經衰弱 焦慮
A number of things. Neuroses, anxiety,
許多人都有的痛苦往事
a painful past like many.
罪惡感
Guilt.
關於什麼的罪惡感
Guilt over what?
班特別喜歡年輕女人
Ben had a weakness for young women.
是收錢的年輕女人
Paying for them, more specifically.
他經常招妓 不過這會引起他
He frequented escorts, although it ignited in him
嚴重的羞愧感和自我厭惡
tremendous shame and self-loathing,
進一步導致了自殘傾向
which resulted in further damaging tendencies.
-如此循環 -他在你這治療多久了
-Old cycles. -How long had he been seeing you?
大概三年
About three years.
對他的治療有效果嗎？
Was he making any progress, his therapy?
我認為有
I like to think so.
他發作沒有以前頻繁了
His relapses were less frequent
之後的自殘傾向也越來越輕了
and he didn't compound them with further damaging behavior.
他的習慣 他有提到過哪個妹子嗎？
His habit, did he ever mention any girls by name?
最喜歡的服務 妹子
Favorite service? Favorite girl?
沒有 我沒印象了
No, not that I recall,
但我可以查以前的治療筆記
but I'd be willing to go back over my notes.
有沒有提到過塔莎這個名字
What about the name Tascha?
提到過她嗎？
He ever mention her?
他提到過暴力嗎？
Did he ever mention violence?
跟妹子 皮條客的矛盾
Trouble with a girl, a pimp?
他對性上癮 但並不是主動的一方
He was sexually obsessed, but he was not aggressive.
他很...被動
More... passive.
班的私人問題
That's about as detailed
我只能說這麼多
as I'll get airing Ben's personal issues.
對我們很有幫助 謝謝
This was helpful. Thank you.
你身份卡寫著安蒂格妮·貝瑟瑞
Your ID said Antigone Bezzerides.
你與艾里奧特·貝瑟瑞有什麼關聯嗎？
Are you related to Elliot Bezzerides by any chance?
-你認識他 -很久以前認識的
-You know him? -I used to a bit a long time ago.
我那時研究善良人公社相關的社會理論
I did some social theory with the Good People.
我記得他有一個女兒
He had a daughter, I remember.
上帝 是你嗎？
Good Lord, was that you?
我不願想起那些
I left all that behind.
那是個混亂的地方
It was a fucked-up place.
世界上各種各樣的秘密
Well, all kinds of secrets in the world.
各種各樣的真相
All kinds of truth.
一共五個孩子一起長大
Five kids living there when I was growing up.
兩個在監獄 兩個自殺了
Two are in jail now, two committed suicide.
社會理論怎麼解釋
How's that for social theory?
-第五個呢 -她成為了一名警探
-And the fifth? -She became a detective.
為避免公眾對本案進行進一步猜測
To curb public speculation in this homicide,
我有必要宣佈本警局
it's become necessary to announce that our offices
正在調查一起涉及洛杉磯芬奇市周邊的
are conducting a criminal probe into the incorporated city
突發新聞 司法部長蓋爾多夫隨即宣佈徹查市執行官謀殺案
刑事案件
of Vinci in LA County.
本次調查早已勢在必行
This investigation is long overdue.
我們請各州
And we ask all state
各市的警局合作...
and city officials to cooperate...
司法部長剛剛宣佈要徹查此案
Attorney general just announced a shakedown.
你不應該把那帶來
You're not supposed to bring that here.
這是放空的10
It's short 10.
你接替吉恩·史萊特里時
When you took over from Gene Slattery,
我們訂了規矩
we established terms.
放空不在其中 法蘭克
Short wasn't part of it, Frank.
我在努力湊
I'm pulling some stuff together.
增加收入來源
Adding revenue streams.
我只需要幾星期
I just need a couple of weeks.
我賣了出租的農場和垃圾處理業務
I sold the rent farms and waste disposal business
再湊上鐵路項目的錢 你也懂的
to pull together the corridor money. You know that.
你仍然有牌室的回扣
You still owe the poker room kickback.
如果有必要你再賣一些地
Sell some of that land if you need to.
卡史伯雷死的時候還欠我的錢
Caspere died with my money in his pocket.
外面有人對牌室感興趣
I've had outside interest re: the poker room.
可能會報個高價
Think they can turn a higher gross.
-高額利息 -什麼外人
-Higher vig. -What outside interest?
跟你說一下 現在是賣方市場
Just so you know, it's a seller's market.
你真要為了一萬塊坑我嗎？
You seriously gonna bust my balls over 10 Gs?
我辛苦經營了六年
I kept this place tight as a drum six years.
非法工人聯盟的事誰壓住的
Who squashed the undocumented workers alliance?
肇事逃逸呢
That hit and run?
你兒子臉上全是白粉
Your son's face was so coke-dusted
跟個小丑似的
he looked like a clown.
東尼 是的
Tony, yeah.
我的兒子恐怕
My son, I fear,
已經失去理智了
is losing his fucking mind.
像他過世的母親
Like his departed mother.
有些人就是受不了高層次的挑戰
Some people can't handle the deep trip.
我恐怕他會毀掉一切
I fear he is a destroyer.
我那個年代 只要敢想就能賺錢
In my day, you understand, it was about consciousness expansion,
探索致富的秘密
tracing the unseen web.
養孩子真是讓人失望
Children are a disappointment.
永遠都不要養孩子 法蘭克
Remain unfettered, Frank.
快找到殺死卡史伯雷的兇手了嗎？
They closer on who killed Caspere?
卡特拉斯接手他的生意
Catalast is taking over his action.
一切都在推進
Everything's happening.
我在奧克蘭給我那倒霉孩子弄家夜店
My farkakte offspring I will set up with a club in Oakland.
讓他去別處當紈褲子弟吧
Let him be a boy prince elsewhere.
殺死卡史伯雷的兇手拿走了我的錢
Whoever killed Caspere, they have my money.
-怎麼會 -控股公司賬面上一片空白
-How's that? -The holding company is empty.
那塊地根本就沒買下來
The land was never purchased
我這輩子的心血全憑空消失了
and I'm fucked out of my life's work.
我需要有人給我指路 奧斯丁
Now I need a direction to turn, Austin.
否則我可能要拉人下水了
Or I may just start pulling down walls.
這可不像聰明人的做法 小子
That doesn't sound like a smart play, gever.
誰都不喜歡含沙射影
Innuendo is nobody's friend.
你不擔心殺死卡史伯雷的人
You're not worried whoever did Caspere
可能會有更大的陰謀嗎？
might be part of something bigger?
暗地裡想從鐵路項目上撈一筆什麼的
Muscling in on the corridor, secret handshakes and whatnot.
班有他自己的慈善機構
Ben had his own charity and what punched his ticket
雇殺手的可能是某一個人
could have come from some personal pocket.
沒人能從我手裡搶 法蘭克
Nobody muscles me, Frank.
州檢察官會收我的錢
State attorney will get his piece,
卡史伯雷的事情也會了結
Caspere will get closed,
世界還是繼續運轉
the world will turn uncaring of our struggles.
卡史伯雷的案子結了之後 我要內線消息
They close Caspere, I want a tip.
我要和兇手單獨待幾分鐘
I want time alone with the guy that did it.
你很勤奮 法蘭克
You are industrious, Frank.
我希望你能熬過這一劫
I want to see you make it through this.
是誰想要接手牌屋
Who wants to move on the poker room?
下周多加一萬五的利息 法蘭克
Kickback's an extra 15 next week, Frank.
再下一周加兩萬兩千五
22.50 the week after.
如果你到時候補不上
You don't come through then,
我就得照顧一下外人了
I have to entertain other interests.
生意場上無情面
It's business.
當然
Sure.
這就稍微能解釋通一點了 對嗎？
Now this is making some sense, right?
解釋了他家牆上的畫
It explains his home decor.
每月取現金很可能就是付嫖資的
Nine to one the cash withdrawal every month was a hooker blowout.
這傢伙經常會接觸犯罪分子
Guy's regularly in touch with criminal elements.
可能是皮條客
Pimps,
闖進去 把他帶到別的地方拷打
they break in, tortured him somewhere.
或許是想讓他說出存錢的地方
Probably trying to get access to assets.
我覺得比這要複雜
I think it's more twisted than that.
他受的折磨 他家裡那堆鬼東西
What was done to him, that shit in his house.
我們恐怕只接觸到了冰山一角
He's into a lot of stuff we're just scratching.
我們可以讓伍卓夫去查妓女和三陪
Well, we can have Woodrugh work prosts, escort services.
他肯定很擅長查這個
He'd be smooth for that.
是啊
Sure.
你聽說過那句蒼蠅和蜂蜜的俗語嗎？
You know that expression about flies and honey?
蜂蜜比醋能更抓到更多蒼蠅
（指對人態度好更容易拉攏人心）
You catch more flies with honey than you do with vinegar
聽過 可是我抓蒼蠅有屁用
Mmm. The fuck do I want with a bunch of flies?
沒有蒼蠅你就沒有誘餌
Well, you don't have flies, you can't fly-fish.
這是什麼鬼地方
What is this fucking place?
郊區人逃到這
Suburban flight,
重工業都遷往內陸或海外
heavy manufacturing moves inland or overseas,
工廠倒閉
plants close.
只有這裡 一群聰明的資本家們
Except here, a bunch of good capitalists
被廉價地租 減稅刺激政策
ran in for cheap leases, tax incentives,
移民勞動力 血汗工廠吸引過來
immigrant labor, sweatshop economics.
你對這些沒有意見嗎？
You don't have a problem with that?
沒有 我強烈懷疑
No, my strong suspicion is
每個人的生活都是咎由自取
we get the world we deserve.
你為什麼來這個地方
Why are you here? This place?
我在洛杉磯警局工作過
I did time in the LA Sheriff's.
只是想多賺點
I just needed better pay.
工作時間規律點
Regular hours.
我有個兒子
I had a son.
他們肯定跟你說過我的事吧
They told you about me, I'm sure.
說過 上面說你是個不錯的調查員
Yeah, bosses said you're a solid investigator.
你肯定不這麼認為 但我絕不扯淡
I know you wouldn't think it, but I don't bullshit.
你要是扯淡了怎麼辦
What would you say if you did?
我能告訴你我那操蛋婚姻的故事嗎？
Can I tell you what you may or may not have heard,
你可能聽過 就算沒有也肯定會聽說
but almost definitely will hear about my busted marriage?
傳聞說我殺了傷害我妻子的那個混蛋
Rumors have me killing this piece of filth hurt my wife.
還說我給南城的一個黑幫做事
Same rumors put me in hock to a Southland mob.
而且如果你問對了人 你還可能聽說
And if you know who to ask, you might hear I like to wet
我有一大堆的惡習
now and then from a number of bad habits.
-這些傳聞有真的嗎 -有
-Any of that true? -Oh, yeah.
-哪部分 -一堆惡習
-Which parts? -Bad habits.
一樣都沒戒掉過
Never lost one yet.
你呢
You?
我分不清什麼習慣是好的
Oh, I don't distinguish between good and bad habits.
帶那麼多刀是怎麼回事
What's with all the knives?
要是你遇見的每個人都能制服你
Could you do this job if everyone you encountered
你還能幹好這份工作嗎？
could physically overpower you?
別說當好警察了
I mean, forget police work.
任何人光是處在那樣的境地都會發瘋的
No man could walk around like that without going nuts.
所以這些是用來制衡的 有道理
So they're equalizers. Makes sense.
不 不幹這行我也會帶著
No, I'd still wear them if I wasn't on the job.
男女間最根本的區別就是
Fundamental difference between the sexes
一方可以空手殺死另一方
is that one of them can kill the other with their bare hands.
不管塊頭多大的男人敢碰我
Man of any size lays hands on me,
我讓他一分鐘內流血身亡
he's gonna bleed out in under a minute.
你要知道 我支援女權
Well, just so you know, I support feminism.
我跟眾多女性一樣覺得自己身材不好
Mostly by having body image issues.
皮特勒提到的那個是什麼
What's that thing Pitlor mentioned?
你的父親 善良人公社
Your dad, the Good People?
七八十年代末 在蓋爾南維爾附近
It was this, like, commune around Guerneville
建的一個公社
in the late '70s, '80s.
嬉皮士之類的
Hippie shit.
你得自己照顧自己 是嗎？
You had to look out for yourself, huh?
那是你
That's you.
芬奇市 邁向明天
我試圖讓我們兩個更瞭解對方
Look, I'm trying to effect transparency between us.
原因是...
The reason being...
我不知道你知不知道
I don't know if you know this,
但是我們 這次調查
but us, the investigation,
我不覺得會有什麼結果
I don't think it's supposed to work.
為什麼
Why is that?
這是州檢察官命令的調查
State Attorney's investigation.
他們肯定監聽了你 那個小孩也是
They must have tapped you. You know, the kid, too.
他們為什麼不找州里的大陪審團調查
Why wouldn't they have a team of state grand jury investigators
偏偏找了你和那個小孩
working Vinci instead of just you and the kid?
為什麼州檢察官不全程施壓
Why wouldn't the SA do a full-court press on this?
你想說實話
You want honest?
告訴我 你肯讓步多少
Tell me, how compromised are you?
好吧 晚安
Anyways, good night.
這是什麼 你為什麼不告訴我
What is that? Why didn't you tell me?
我操
What the fuck?
加州高速巡警隊員 以拘捕要挾萊西·林德爾與其發生關係
因為這只是一堆狗屁不通的狗屎
'Cause that right there is a bunch of unbridled horseshit.
你知道那妹子嗎？
You read about the girl?
自己犯了事要進監獄
Goes to jail for one more fuckup,
就倒打一耙說是我的錯 僅此而已
tries to say I did something wrong. That's it.
那你為什麼不告訴我
Then why didn't you tell me?
因為我不想再想這件事
'Cause I don't want to think about it.
-你會失業嗎 -不會
-Are you gonna lose your job? -No.
我在州檢察官那接到個新任務
I got a new assignment through the state attorney.
我以後就是偵探了
I'm gonna be a detective after.
聽著 報紙提到了
Listen, this paper talks about you
你參與了蒙特內格羅安全隊的事
being in this Black Mountain Security thing.
我告訴過你 我不會再提蒙特內格羅的事了
I told you, I don't talk about the desert.
但是這個蒙特內格羅安全隊做了很多壞...
But this Black Mountain Security, they did things, bad--
所以就這樣 你就這樣走了嗎？
So that's it? You're just taking off?
我告訴過你了
Come on, I just told you.
我要去洛杉磯工作一段時間
I got to go to LA to work for a while.
特殊事件 特殊調查
Special detail. Special investigator.
-就是這樣 -你身上酒氣熏天
-That's it. -God, you smell like a bar rag.
誰說伏特加沒有味道 全是放屁
They say vodka don't smell, but that's bullshit.
你聞著就像我叔叔
You smell just like my uncle.
我只是去南方待一段時間
I'm just going down south a while.
僅此而已
That's it.
-那你的公寓呢 -還是在那啊
-And your apartment? -Still there, Em.
你到底在做什麼
What are you doing?
我受不了了 我盡力了
I can't do this anymore. I tried.
工作的事
It's work.
這是件好事 小愛
It's a good thing, Em.
不
No.
你幾乎不說話
You barely talk.
我不瞭解你家人 你也不想瞭解我的
I don't know your family. You don't want to know mine.
-你到底是誰 -滾蛋吧
-Who are you? -Oh, fuck off.
我他媽還能是誰
Who the fuck am I supposed to be?
-我不知道你會是誰 -我的天啊
-I don't know who you're supposed to be. -Jesus Christ.
沒錯 滾蛋 滾
Yeah, fuck off. Go.
不管你發生了什麼 我都不會管你
God, whatever happened to you, I can't fix it.
我沒什麼問題
There's nothing wrong with me.
我這週末打電話給你
I'll call you this weekend.
別 我不想再和你聯絡了 保羅
Don't. I don't want to hear from you, Paul.
你不能給我更好的生活
You can't give me more than this.
你不 你不正常
You're not--you're not right.
有時候我和你在一起 我能感到...
Sometimes I'm with you and I can tell that...
隨便吧
Fuck it.
我要走了
I gotta go.
別再回來
Don't come back.
是你的問題 不是我的
It's on you, not me.
我不能再見你了 保羅
I can't see you again, Paul.
和你一起 受傷的總是我
You hurt me seeing you.
這是你自找的
You're doing this.
不是我
This isn't me doing this.
This isn't me.
法蘭克
Frank.
把我丟進這坑裡 居然還來看我
Surprised you're visiting this pit you stuck me with.
在這工作累死人了
It's hard work up in here.
我必須說 回到這我一點都不懷念
I gotta say, being back in here, I don't miss it.
就像是多年的頭痛病又犯了
Seems like a headache looking back.
沒錯就是讓人頭痛
Fucking right it's a headache.
供應商 訂購單 許可證
Vendors, purchase orders, licenses.
每個妞都等著白馬王子拯救
Every one of these bitches think this is "Pretty Woman."
我要知道你手下的妹子認不認識一個男的
I need to know if any of your girls knew a guy
喜歡年輕貨
liked young trim.
大概 幾個月以前
Maybe, like, a few months ago.
他在他家約過一次
He booked a date at his place.
在芬奇 那個大房子
In Vinci? The big house?
不 一個小地方 在好萊塢
No, this place small. In Hollywood.
二手房
Took-over home.
你記得在哪裡嗎？
You remember where it was?
沒關係 說吧
Go ahead, girl, speak.
我把地址記下來了
I write them down.
丹尼說 要注意周圍環境
Danny says you pay attention to streets,
永遠清楚自己在哪
always know where you are.
那人有沒有做什麼可怕的事
This guy, he do anything scary?
或者任何可能惹毛別人的事
Anything might have pissed somebody off?
沒有 他其實有點...
No. He kind of...
虛弱 是吧
weak, you say?
只想看而已
Just want to watch.
把你見他的地址寫下來
Write it down where you met him.
法蘭克 這次可是我幫了你 對吧
I hope this goodwill does not go unnoticed on your end, Frank.
出來混 得有朋友嘛
Everybody needs friends, see?
這裡是好萊塢分局刑警隊
This is Hollywood Division Vice Squad.
請在提示音響後留言
Please leave your message
我們會盡快回復
after the beep and we'll get back to you.
我是州警局的貝瑟瑞警探
This is Detective Bezzerides
負責93009號特別任務
with state police detail 93009.
我想和你們的警探聊聊
I was hoping to speak with a vice detective---
如您對本次服務滿意 請按1
If you are satisfied with your message, press one.
任何口味 任何需求 辣妹卡利·安琪兒都能滿足
任何時間 任何地點 辣妹卡利·安琪兒都能出現
-怎麼了 -記得那個失蹤少女嗎？
-Yeah. -Yo, you remember that missing girl?
我和她以前的舍友聊過了
I talked to her old roommate.
她說幾個月前 維拉給她打過電話
Said Vera last called her a couple months ago.
問有沒有人找過她
Asked if anybody'd come around looking for her.
我查了她的電話記錄
I checked her phone records
發現有一個來自蓋爾南維爾的電話
and a call came from a Guerneville address.
你那邊怎麼樣
How's it going down there?
麻煩得很
It's a pain in the ass, you know?
進展不大
Not much so far.
可能是妓女或者皮條客乾的
It's--might be a hooker job, some pimp.
今天先這樣吧 明天再碰吧
Let me let you go. Catch up tomorrow?
好
Sure.
再見
Bye.
你能去查查這裡嗎？
How's that for detecting?
卡史伯雷還有個住處 專門和妓女鬼混的
Caspere had another house. Place he brought girls.
-你去查了嗎 -不 我不想去
-You check it out? -No, I don't want to go near it.
我的人也不太擅長處理證據
And my people ain't exactly proficient in evidence handling.
你可以以警察的身份去
Figured you'd go in as police,
看看能找到什麼有用的東西
see what you can, see what I might need to know.
和他買地
Grab anything that pushed
和他的生意有關的東西都拿走
towards Caspere's dealing with land purchases.
這又是怎麼回事
Yeah, what's going on with that?
錢 他那塊地皮值很多錢
Money. Place is about to be worth a whole lot more.
這是好萊塢啊 什麼意思
This is Hollywood. So?
我一直都想問問你
Listen, I've been wanting to ask you,
如果一切都隨我願
things shake out like I expect,
明年此時 你可能就是芬奇警局局長了
this time next year, might be Chief of PD--Vinci.
你覺得怎麼樣
How'd that be?
局長 法蘭克 我不想當局長
Chief? I don't want that, Frank.
我管你想不想當 你怎麼了
Did I ask you if you want that? What's up with you, huh?
我可是在幫你上位
I'm lining stuff up for you here.
局長一年能撈三十萬
That job pays 300K a year.
有這筆錢 你能請一大幫家庭律師了
You could hire a hell of a family lawyer for that.
這個怎麼樣
That, right there.
你...你還記得我們倆是怎麼搞到一起的嗎？
You--you remember how we got together?
我記得你要拋屍
I remember you dumping a body.
我給你辦事的原因
The reasons for all this, all that,
對我來說沒有任何意義了
might not exist for me anymore.
你明白了嗎？
You see?
我沒理由一直為你做事
I got no reason to keep at this.
你是說你覺得蹲一輩子大獄
Meaning you'd consider life in prison, what,
還不錯嗎？
a positive?
我可沒那麼說
No, I ain't saying that either.
這麼說 你還有我不知道的後路
What, you have other options here I'm not privy to?
真逼到那份上
Everybody's got the one option,
都能找到後路
you want it bad enough.
你以前可是條漢子
You used to be a hard man.
-我現在累了 -那就給我好好休息
-I'm tired. -Then get some sleep.
先查了那地方再說
after you check the place out.
完事以後來找我
Get back to me.
還有 雷
And, Ray...
以後別再和我說這種屁話
I don't want to hear you talk like that again.
雷 再來一瓶啤酒嗎？
You want another beer, Ray?
不用了 我...我得走了
No, I--I gotta take off, I guess.
他的事可真多啊
He's keeping you busy.
是啊 太太
Yes, ma'am.
你應該放鬆一下
You ought to take some time.
去度個假
A vacation.
你去過聖米格爾德阿連德[墨西哥]嗎？
Have you ever been to San Miguel de Allende?
-沒有 -那是我的家鄉
-No. -That's where I'm from.
那裡有高山 瀑布 廣場
Mountains, waterfalls, this plaza.
是嗎 聽起來不錯
Well, that sounds really nice.
也許哪天我能帶你去看看
Maybe I could show it to you sometime.
除非我死了 否則沒法休假
I think the only way I get a vacation is if I croak.
那你就該換個工作
You should get another job, then.
親愛的 來不及了
It's too late for that, darlin'.
還有好多事也都來不及了
That and about a million other things.
你的錢
Your money.
不是我的
That's not mine.